Mahadev

mahadevgadge45@gmail.com | 9738265528 | Bengaluru, India https://github.com/Mahadev-Gadge

SUMMARY

Having 4+ Years of Industry experience, 2 years of experience in medical device manufacturing and 2.5 years of experience as a Python developer. Looking for carrier transition to Data scientist or machine learning role with strong foundation in statistical analysis, machine learning with programming languages such as Python & SQL.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python developer at Lifesignals Bengaluru, India

Jan 2021 - Present

- Gathered clinical team requirements, designed and implemented sensorprocessing validation framework, which is responsible for producing information about patient health using clinical data.
- Framework collects required data from clinical data, it preprocess, analyze and finds interesting facts and dumps statistical evidence into csv report and pdf files. Statistical reports gives very good understandings to physician about patient health and helps in taking necessary actions.
- Created and developed functional test cases for validation framework using python Unittest framework.
- Co-ordinated with clinical team to understand the requirements and provide technical solutions.
- Good knowledge on OOPs, logging, regular_expressions, multiprocessing and multithreading.

Data science intern at Datamites Bengaluru, India

Jan 2023 - Present

- Having in depth knowledge in statistical machine learning models: KNN, Naive Bayes, Logistic and linear regression, SVM, Decision tress, Ensemble techniques & etc.
- Hands on experience in presenting information using data visualization techniques.
- Hands on experience in building end to end machine learning models.

Manufacturing project engineer at GE Healthcare Bengaluru, India

July 2018 - July 2020

- Created and implemented process in manufacturing lines for MRI machine with adhering to Quality system ISO 13485.
- Work experience in vendor management, planning, purchasing, supply chain managament and logistics.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Data science/Machine learning:

Python, Data analytics, Data preparation, Data mining, Data visualization, Dimensionality reduction techniques, Feature engineering, Feature selection, supervised and unsupervised ML algorithms & NLP.

• Mathematics for Data science:

Linear algebra, Probability and statistics.

• Python packages and Frameworks:

Scikit-Learn, matplotlib, seaborn, NumPy, Pandas, Scipy, Spacy, RegEx, NLTK and Unittest.

• Database and Deployment:

MySQL, Git, GitHub, BitBucket, Jira.

Tools:

Jupyter notebook, Anaconda, VS code, bitbucket, Vim.

EDUCATION

Nitte Meenakshi Institute of technology Bengaluru, India

Graduted June 2018

Electronics & Communication Egineering

Cum GPA: 8.51/10.0

SOFT SKILLS

- Optimistic
- Problem solving
- Time management

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified Data Scientist Certification from IABAC.